[
  {
    "id" : 0,
    "question" : "What is the minimum weight for any sling load to fly?",
    "answer" : "500 lbs"
  },
  {
    "id" : 1,
    "question" : "What is the hook capacity of the UH-60L/M?\n",
    "answer" : "9,000 lbs"
  },
  {
    "id" : 2,
    "question" : "What are the three types of lacing ropes you can use with the A-22 cargo bag?",
    "answer" : "Type III nylon, 3/8 inch hemp rope, 7/16 in nylon rope"
  },
  {
    "id" : 3,
    "question" : "What are the factors of in-flight stability?",
    "answer" : "Humidity, Altitude and Temperature"
  },
  {
    "id" : 4,
    "question" : "What reference material covers single point rigging procedures?",
    "answer" : "TM 4-48.10"
  },
  {
    "id" : 5,
    "question" : "What is the rank requirement for a qualified sling load inspector?",
    "answer" : "SPC or above"
  },
  {
    "id" : 6,
    "question" : "What is the diameter of the 10k apex pin portion?",
    "answer" : "1 1/8 in "
  },
  {
    "id" : 7,
    "question" : "What are the three units involved in a sling load operation?",
    "answer" : "Supported unit, Aviation unit, Receiving unit"
  },
  {
    "id" : 8,
    "question" : "What is the primary lift point on the 500 gallon fuel blivet?",
    "answer" : "5/8 screw pin clevis"
  },
  {
    "id" : 9,
    "question" : "What size landing point is required for a CH-47 with a long line sling load during nighttime operations?",
    "answer" : "Size 7"
  },
  {
    "id" : 10,
    "question" : "Why must your sleeves be rolled down when working around aircraft?",
    "answer" : "Protect from flying debris & flash fires."
  },
  {
    "id" : 11,
    "question" : "What reference material covers Aircraft Safety?",
    "answer" : "FM 3-99"
  },
  {
    "id" : 12,
    "question" : "In the acronym DROP, what does the R stand for?",
    "answer" : "Reduce Unnecessary Gear"
  },
  {
    "id" : 13,
    "question" : "What are the three portions of the aircraft that you must avoid at all times?",
    "answer" : "Main rotor blade, tail rotor blade, and cargo hook (static electricity)."
  },
  {
    "id" : 14,
    "question" : "In case of a fire, when should you exit the aircraft?",
    "answer" : "Immediately."
  },
  {
    "id" : 15,
    "question" : "Define an Air Assault Operation?",
    "answer" : "Movement of friendly assault forces by rotary wing aircraft to engage enemy forces or to seize and hold key terrain."
  },
  {
    "id" : 16,
    "question" : "What is a chalk/load defined as?",
    "answer" : "Personnel and equipment designated to be moved by a specific aircraft."
  },
  {
    "id" : 17,
    "question" : "What are the six factors that determine abort criteria?",
    "answer" : "Weather, time, available aircraft, mission essential combat power, mission criticality, and enemy."
  },
  {
    "id" : 18,
    "question" : "What are the components of an Air Route?",
    "answer" : "SP, RP, ACP, and flight path."
  },
  {
    "id" : 19,
    "question" : "What are the three terrain flight modes?",
    "answer" : "Low level, contour, and NAP of the Earth."
  },
  {
    "id" : 20,
    "question" : "What reference material covers Aircraft Orientation?",
    "answer" : "FM 3-04."
  },
  {
    "id" : 21,
    "question" : "What is the cruise speed of the AH-6J/MH-6J?",
    "answer" : "135 knots."
  }
]